kesslercrane.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy — Kessler

**Privacy Notice**

Effective May 25, 2018

This Privacy Notice (the “ **Privacy Notice** ”) describes how Kessler Crane, Inc. and our associated entities collect, use, and share your information.

This Privacy Notice applies to your use of the Kessler Crane, Inc. websites, our mobile applications, and all other digital and online services provided by Kessler Crane, Inc. (collectively, the “ **Services** ”) and describes our privacy practices relating to the Services. It does not apply to information collected by Kessler Crane, Inc. offline, or to third party websites, applications, or services (including any other affiliates’ or organizations not named above). 

 **Applicability & Eligibility**

We need to process your personal data to operate our organization and provide you with certain Services. Before accessing, using, or interacting with the Services you should carefully review the terms and conditions of this Privacy Notice. Your use of the Services is further governed by our Terms and Conditions, which is also incorporated into your agreement with Kessler Crane, Inc. by this reference. 

By accepting our Privacy Notice and Terms and Conditions, you are confirming that you have read and understood these policies, including how and why we use your information. If you don’t want us to collect or process your personal data in the ways described in this Privacy Notice, you should not use the Services. Please note we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies or practices of any third party organization or service. 

The Services are not directed to children under the age of 16. You may not use the Services if you are under the age of 16. If you are under the age of 18, you should not provide any information on our Services. 

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, register at an event or trade show, participate in a promotion or sweepstakes or participate in another site feature.  
When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information.   
We may collect and store information related to purchases of the Services. You may be required to provide certain information to complete payments via the Services, including your credit or debit card number, card expiration date, CVV code, and billing address (collectively, “ **Payment Information** ”), along with your name and billing, delivery and shipping address, to complete payment transactions through certain services. The Companies store your encrypted Payment Information in compliance with the industry standards. 

Please note The Companies work with Service Providers (as defined below) to handle payment transactions. You are subject to the Privacy Policies and Terms and Conditions of our Service Providers when utilizing a third party service through The Companies’ Services. Please review the Service Providers’ Privacy Policies and Terms and Conditions before using their services. 

We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.

IP Addresses: We automatically collect the IP addresses of users of certain Services, such as website visitors, those that log in to the Services, and those who post messages to the communities and forums. We process this information on the basis of our legitimate interests in protecting the Services and providing the Services to you. 

Unique Identifiers: When you use or access the Services, we may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or remotely store one or more “Unique Identifiers,” such as a universally unique identifier (“UUID”). A Unique Identifier may remain on your device persistently, to help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Services. Some features of the Services may not function properly if use or availability of Unique Identifiers is impaired or disabled. 

Log File Information: When you use our Services, we may receive log file information such as your IP address, browser type, access times, domain names operating system, the referring web page(s), pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device information (including device and application IDs), search terms, and cookie information. We receive log file data when you interact with our Services, for example, when you visit our website, sign into our Services, or interact with our email notifications. Kessler Crane, Inc. uses log file data to provide, understand, and improve our Services, and to customize the content we show you. Kessler Crane, Inc. may link this log file to other information Kessler Crane, Inc. collects about you via the Services. 

Public Information: The Companies may also collect information about you from publicly available sources. Information you make publicly available in any public or open forum, such as on a social network, may be considered public information for the purposes of this Privacy Notice, and may be accessed and collected by The Companies. Please be aware that any content or information you share with or provide to third parties using or related to your use of the Services are neither private, nor confidential. The Companies is not responsible for any content or information you post or share with third parties. If you do not wish for certain information to be public, please do not share it publicly. 

Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

 **How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:  
To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.  
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.  
To quickly process your transactions.  
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.  
If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.

 **How do we protect visitor information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.

 **Do we use "cookies"?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.

KesslerCrane.com uses Google Analytics features based on Google's Display Advertising (e.g. Remarketing, Advertising Features Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.

Using the Ads Settings visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads.

 **Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include Kessler Crane, Inc. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

Kessler Crane, Inc. may purchase other businesses or their assets, sell our business assets, or be involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets (a “ **Business Transaction** ”). Your information, including personal data, may be among assets sold or transferred as part of a Business Transaction. In some cases, Kessler Crane, Inc. may choose to buy or sell assets. Such transactions may be necessary and in our legitimate interests, particularly our interest in making decisions that enable our organization to develop over the long term. 

We may disclose aggregated, non-personal data received from providing the Services, including information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. Kessler Crane, inc. may share demographic information with business partners, but it will be aggregated and de-personalized, so that personal data is not revealed. 

 **Your rights and how can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?**

Kessler Crane, inc. seek to ensure all individuals are provided with the rights mandated by their governing jurisdiction. Not all of the rights discussed in this Privacy Notice will apply to each individual data subject and may not apply to you depending upon your jurisdiction. 

You may benefit from a number of rights in relation to your information that we process. Some rights apply only in certain limited cases, depending on your location. If you would like to manage, change, limit, or delete your personal data, you can do so by contacting us. Upon request, Kessler Crane, Inc. will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal data. In certain cases where we process your information, you may also have a right to restrict or limit the ways in which we use your personal data. In certain circumstances, you also have the right to request the deletion of your personal data, and to obtain a copy of your personal data in an easily accessible format. 

If we process your information based on our legitimate interests as explained in this Privacy Notice, or in the public interest, you can object to this processing in certain circumstances. In such cases, we will cease processing your information unless we have compelling legitimate grounds to continue processing or where it is needed for legal reasons. Where we use your data for direct marketing purposes, you can always object using the unsubscribe link in such communications or changing your account settings. 

Where you have provided consent to certain data processing, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time by contacting Kessler Crane, Inc. at: privacy@kesslercrane.com. A withdrawal of consent will not affect the validity of our use of your personal data up until the point you have withdrawn your consent. 

If you no longer wish to use the Services or receive service-related messages (except for legally required notices), then you may contact us using the information above. 

To modify your e-mail subscriptions, you can click on the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our promotional e-mails.

To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.

Kessler Crane, Inc. does not currently employ a process for automatically responding to “Do Not Track” (DNT) signals sent by web browsers, mobile devices, or other mechanisms. Per industry standards, third parties may be able to collect information, including personal data, about your online activities over time and across different websites or online services when you use Services. You may opt out of online behavioral ads at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. You also may limit certain tracking by disabling cookies in your web browser. 

 **Third party links**

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

 **Changes to our policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on May 25, 2018.

 **Questions and feedback**

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue at privacy@kesslercrane.com or calling 574-400-2251.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

 **Your consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
